<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel Places</string>
    <string name="placesToGo">Top 5 places To Travel in 2016</string>
    <string name="estonia_info">
       \n  Visitors to <b>Estonia</b> encounter a mix of urbanity and wilderness, of the medieval and the contemporary,\n
        with crumbling castles and colourful design permeating urban landscapes.\n
        An efficient transport system makes it easy to get around, and the tech-savvy,
        dynamic residents welcome visitors with open arms.\n
        Friction between older generations of Russians and Estonians is a throwback to the Soviet era,\n
        while younger people mix freely, and those who get past the Estonians’ natural reserve find them to be gregarious,
        uninhibited hosts.
        \n
        Read more: <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Estonia"> Click Here</a></string>
    <string name="hochi_info">
        "\n Welcome to one of Asia's most compelling cities.
        <b>Ho Chi Minh City</b> is the energetic commercial hub of modern Vietnam, with wide boulevards, grand colonial buildings,fascinating cultural sights, and a vibrant tangle of narrow laneways – all framed by a kinetic river of traffic.
        Exploring the streets from the back seat of a Vespa is an exhilarating way to get a feel for a city with nearly 5 million motorbikes.
        To get your orientation fast, jump on an organised tour with an emphasis on food, nightlife,
        iconic sights or unusual attractions; a guide can help you discover the hot spots."

        Read more:<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ho_Chi_Minh_City">Click Here</a> </string>
    <string name="africa_info">
     " \n <b>East Africa</b> is world famous for its spectacular wildlife and panoramas:
        the annual migration of two million zebras and wildebeest in the Serengeti and Maasai Mara Game Reserves, the breathtaking natural wonder of the gigantic Ngorongoro Crater,
        the largest unbroken volcanic caldera in the world, teeming with wildlife in its center,the majestic snow-capped Mount Kilimanjaro.
        The continent’s unique, dazzling wildlife and landscapes are precious natural resources, and add much to the mystique of Africa.
        The variety of East Africa’s marine life is incredible, consisting of delicate seahorses,razor- and pipe-fish, dazzling angel- and butterfly-fish, mudskippers, and
        the giants of the open sea—sharks, tuna, black marlin, and the odd-looking sunfish, Mola mola,which is the world’s largest and heaviest bony fish, known to reach weights over a ton.
        The inshore waters support more than 11,000 known species of plants and animals, an estimated 10percent to 15percentof which are thought to be endemic to this ecoregion."

        Read more:<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/East_Africa">Click Here</a> </string>

    <string name="mexico_info">
      "\n  Boasting one of most incredibly scenic and diverse landscapes in North America,New Mexico offers endless opportunities for exploration and adventure.
        With strong influences of both Native American and Hispanic culture,the state offers the visitor a multitude of unique attractions both in large cities like Santa Fe and Albuquerque as well as the smaller hubs of UFO-focused Roswell and the artists' colony of Taos.
        Center of the American Southwest, the Land of Enchantment didn't gain statehood until 1912.
        Today, New Mexico offers the visitor fantastic nature experiences, distinctive cuisine,and an impressive fine arts scene.
        White Sands National Monument is one of the most stunning landscapes in the state,located a half an hour's drive southwest of Alamogordo in the south of New Mexico.\n "

         Read more:<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Mexico">Click Here</a></string>
    <string name="bosnia_info">
       " \n Bosnia and Herzegovina , a country on the Balkan Peninsula in southeastern Europe, encompasses mountainous terrain,medieval villages and Muslim and Christian landmarks.
        Its countryside is marked by deep gorges,turquoise rivers and lakes, and the Dinaric Alps forests and crags.
        It's a popular destination for outdoor sports such as hiking, mountain biking, white-water rafting and skiing.
        Bosnian towns are lovably small, wrapped around medieval castles and surrounded by mountain ridgesor cascading river canyons.
        Few places in Europe offer better rafting or such accessible, inexpensive skiing. "
        \n
       Read more:<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bosnia_and_Herzegovina">Click Here</a></string>
</resources>
